Can you go and check up on the conductor's room with him?
It's dangerous, dangerous!
Barnes managed to save two bottles of the finished product from the fire.
Where is your little girl?
She was taken away by those people in the white suits.
脅されて つい ?
You were threatened, and so accidentally...
Yes... When it comes to Gustavo Baggetta's monstrous power...
普通ではありませんので
このままでは殺されると思つ亡 つい…
It's just too much...
Afraid that I'd be killed if he continued, I accidentally...
だ力らって イブちゃんを
危険にさらすようなこと言うなん亡
That's no reason to say things that might put little Eve in danger!
いやあ 申し訳ない
ちゃんと手は打つてあるガら
I know... I have no excuse.
I've taken proper measures though.
たとえ命の危険を感じたと しても
Even if you think your life may be in danger...
あんな いたいけな女の子を
言い訳に使うのは
to use such a lovely little girl to get out of it...
工レアン君同様 感心しないね
Like Elean, I can't sympathize with you.
この件に関しての責任は
あくまでも二コラス君 個人が取ること
It is obvious that Nicholas should take full responsibility in this case.
Pay close attention to your actions.
重々注意し亡事に当たりたまえ
分力つたね
You understand, right?
Understood.
力しこまりました
連絡は ?
Any news?
ありません
まだ動きはないようです
None.
It seems they haven't moved yet.
何力少しでも動きがあっ たら教えろ
Tell me if anything happens.
グス夕一ヴオとガンド一ルが
ダラス絡みで もめ亡くれれば
If Gustavo and the Gandors get into a dispute over Dallas, there should be some information leak.
細力い情報のー つや2つは
出亡くるはずだ
ー つも漏らさず私に伝えるんだ
Tell me all of it.
分力りました
Understood.
ノレム レ一ス Gの無線の声丿
助ノプごくカ ノ こちら貨物室…
こ ちら貨物菫
Save me!
This is the luggage room! This is the luggage room!
Spike!
スパイクだ どうした?
What's wrong?!
ノレム レ 一ス Gの無線の声丿
筧蒼え庭 ノ 2入 とも筧蒼え ちま フ庭ノ
They disappeared! Both of them of disappeared!
すぐノご応接き 応接きよこ レ ごく杓
Reinforcements! Send reinforcements right away!
落ち着け!
何があった 何があったんだ!?
Calm down! What happened?
What happened?!
Stop it! Stay away from me!
や やめろ… 近づくな
やめろ やめろ やめろおおおっ~~!
Stop, stop!
つううつ うううつ ううっ…
うわつ うわああああああああああ…
うゎああ ! うあああ‥
お断りします
I have to decline.
一体 何の義理があ つ て
Why do you think that we should help you with your little revenge?
それは…
That is...
よそ者の フイ一ロって奴が
ここで好き勝手やつ乙る力ら
Because that outsider Firo is doing whatever he wants here—
構成員でもない皆さんが
There's no need for people like you who aren't even members to worry about our problems.
我々の事業の心配をする
必要はないでしょう
じやあ こうしましよう ラツクさん
Well then, let's do it like this, Mr. Luck.
俺らに力を貸し亡くれるなら
俺らは あなたの組織の下につきますよ
If you decide to help us, we will join your organization.
悪い話じやないでしよう
Sounds like a good offer, right?
あのねえ ダラスさん…
Listen here now, Mr. Dallas.
正直な話 我々がどうして皆さんに
声をかけな力ったの力
Speaking honestly, have you ever thought about why we never asked you to join us?
者えたことあります力?
あっ?
あなた方の傍若無人な振る舞いに
目をつむつ亡いたのは
The reason we didn't interfere with your outrageous behavior was...
我々が皆さんを恐れていた力らだとでも
思つてたんじゃないでしょうね?
You couldn't have been thinking it was because we feared you?
はつきり言っておきますが
あなた方を組織に誘わなかったのは
I will tell you clearly now. The reason we didn't invite you to our organization was,
利用価値が力ケラも
見いだせなかったからです
because we didn't even see the slightest use for you.
なつ ?
Thanks to that group of robbers you're running,
は
あなた方が追い剥きまがいのことを
し亡くれ亡いるお力げで
the police is too busy dealing with you folk.
警察の目がそちらに引きつけられる
That's why we didn't interfere.
だ力ら手を出さな力つた
せいぜいがその程度のものですよ
あなた方なんてものは
That's all you are, to us, decoys. Nothing more.
You don't know anything about us!
あんたに俺らの何が分かる…
明ら力に年下に見える少年に
What I do know is that you were done in by a man who was clearly much younger than yourself.
コテンパンにされたということは
よく分力りますカヾ
てめえ… おおっ !
You—
べル兄
Berga.
ラック
何だ この礼儀知らずどもは
Luck.
Who are these rude guys?
知らない人
Don't know 'em.
ふ一 ん
おや ?
酒力 ?
Liquor?
No clue...
さあ?
さあ メリ一 この中に入って
Mary, hide in here.
You'll be able to hide in there on your own.
君ー 人なら何とガ隠れられるよ
B-But, Czes-kun...
で でも… チ工ス君は?
僕は先の檬子を見てくる力ら
メリ一はここで隠れ亡い亡
I'm going to take a look at how things are now.
You hide here, Mary.
絶対に動いちやダメだよ
Stay really still now.
It's all right. I'll be right back, okay?
大丈夫 すぐ戻つ亡くる力ら ね?
Okay.
ノチ工 ス丿
こカ さ邪簾なヵ牛な片 フ乙 )奉
That's one nuisance taken care of.
Now I only have to find the Immortals.
ぁ ご は ~不死者 'き探 すだソプだ
ジヤグジ一力!?
Jacuzzi.
Nick!
二ツク! 無事だつたんだね!
You were all right!
ああ 泡食つたぜ
I had lost my mind.
見張りはどこへ行ったんです力?
Where did the lookouts go?
いや… それが俺にも
よく分力らねえんです
I don't really know either.
Thank you. Fuck you. A villain has arrived!
サンキユ一 フアツキユ一
くせ者参上!
Well, well, well.
あれあれあれ?
見張り誰もいねえじゃん
There's not even one lookout.
つまんねえの
How boring.
But anyway, I'm glad you're all right, Lua!
それにしても無事でよかったなあ
丿し一ウアァァ~
Thanks for saving us, Ladd.
助力つたぜ ラツド
お おい こっちの纏も
ほどいてくれよ!
Hey! Untie my ropes as well, please!
はぁ? 何で? 何か得あんの?
Why?
Is there anything in it for us?
女だったらキスのー つでも
期待すっけどよぉ
If you were a woman, I could hope for a kiss or so,
but you're a guy!
お前 男じやん!
むしろ そのまま死ねばぁ?
On the contrary, you could just die there.
I mean, just die!
つ一力 死んじやえっ
お前が死ぬのは運命だ !
It is your destiny to die here!
誰なんだろう? そいつ
Who could that be?
Who knows...
ジヤ ジヤグジ一
J-Jacuzzi...
見一つけた !
Found you!
いやあああ !
You shouldn't scream.
悲嗚はいけないなあ
I shouldn't do this to Ladd, but is it all right if I take this girl for myself?
ラツ ドにゃ悪いが この娘は
俺がもらつちまつていいよな?
Unlike Ladd, I like to hurt and kill those weaker than—
俺はラツ ドの奴と違つて
弱い奴だけを
いたぶり殺すのが好きなん…
いたぞ あいつらだ !
There he is! That's them!
いよお! そいつら
お前の連れだったのかい
Hey, so he was one of yours, Jacuzzi-kun?
ジヤグジ一君よお!?
うつ… どうして僕の名前を ?
How do you know my name?
Oops, I've forgotten to introduce myself.
おっとつと?
自己紹介が遅れたかなあ?
I'm Ladd Russo.
俺はラツ ドルツソ
You already know why I know you now, right?
これでもう俺が何でお前のことを
知つてる力分力るよなぁ?
Russo...
ルツソ…
ルツ ソフアミリ 一の一員力 !
You're a member of the Russo family?
What are you planning to do onboard this train?
お前ら こんな列車に乗って
何のつもりだぁ?
Rather, who do you think you are?!
いやむしろ何様のつも り だあ ?
この列車は これ力ら俺たちヵヾ
完全に占拠するっつう力
We are going to take complete control of this train.
I mean, we're going to kill half the passengers!
乗客を半分 殺すつ つう力
I mean, depending on the circumstances, we might kill 'em all!
場合によつちゃあ
皆殺しにするっつうか
I mean, if you don't want to get killed by us, jump the hell off of this train and die!
俺らに殺されるつもりがねえなら
とつとと飛ぴ降り亡死ね!
Were you the ones who killed the conductors?
車掌を殺したのは あんたたち力?
Conductors?
車掌? 殺されてたの力?
Were they killed?
Yeah...
行くぞ 車掌室だ
Let's go. We're going to the conductor's room.
You lucked out!
運が良かったなぁ
For now we don't have time to deal with you.
とりあえずお前らの
相手をしてるヒマはなくなつた
Now isn't the time to deal with you for us either.
こっちも今は あなたたちの
相手をしてる場合じゃない
But we will definitely make up for that later!
でも あとで絶対に償ゎせる
Oh? Aren't we bold?
ほお 強気じやねえ力 泣き虫坊や
Crybaby boy!
Let me tell you this, whoever killed the conductor, and whoever did what happened in that room, it wasn't us.
言つとくけどなあ
車掌やったのも
その部屋をやつたのも俺たちじゃねえぜ
You're letting him go like that, Jacuzzi?
いいのかよ ジヤグジ一
For now.
今はいい
先に倒さなきゃならない奴がいる
There's someone else we have to beat first.
That hit 'n run bastard!
あのひき逃げ野郎
今度会つたらひどいぞ!
If we meet again, he's in for some pain!
Some pain!
ひどいぞ !
ぶつ !
I'll hit the car!
手が折れちやうよ !
Your hand will break!
Then I will hit the driver!
じゃあ 運転してる奴をぷつ!
どうやつて 引きずり出すの?
How will you drag him out?
じやあ… 車にツバを吐く!
Then... I will spit on the car!
わあ 完璧だね !
That's perfect!
What are we going to do, Dallas?
どうすんだよ ダラスよお
ガンド一丿しには相手にされねえし…
The Gandors don't want to deal with us...
ぃまぃま
うるせえ! あのクソ忌々しい
フイ一ロのガキが…
Shut up!
That shitty annoying brat Firo...
You just watch!
見てろよ あいつも
ガンド一ルの奴らも
One day I will kill him... and the Gandors!
いつ力ぶち殺し亡やる
にし亡もよお お前んち
金持ちなんだろ?
Even so, your family is rich, right?
遊ぶ金くらい少しは
何と力ならねえのかよ
Can't they give you some money to play around?
先月 強盗様にみ一んな
進呈しちまったとよ!
They said they had donated all of last month's assets to robbers.
つれね一な一
Tough luck...
それでも食うもんくらいは
あんだろ?
You must have enough to eat though...
妹もかゎいいらしいじや一ん
I heard your little sister was cute, too!
イブに近づくな
Stay away from Eve!
お おい
If you do anything to her, I won't let you get away with it!
あいつに何力したら
夕ダじゃおかねえ
わ 分力つたよ!
I understand!
ああああ~~~つ !
Well then, our trip is finally coming to an end.
さて 俺たちの旅も
いよいよ大詰めだ!
長力つたね !
It was pretty long.
Yeah!
ああ!
最初はそう 俺たちは
In the beginning, we were thieves of time,
時間泥棒となつた !
so we stole clocks.
時計を盗んだ時だね !
We once tried to steal an entire museum as well.
美術館を丸ごと
盗もうとした時もあった!
無理だつたね !
That proved impossible though.
ああ! だ力らせめて
もうほ力の奴が入れないように
Yeah...
So at least, in order to make it impossible for others to enter,
we stole the entrance!
入り ロを盗んでやつた !
重力つたね !
It sure was heavy!
After reflecting on our actions, we decided to do good things from then on,
反省した俺たちが これ力らは
良いことをしようと思ってやったのが
大金持ちの遺産を盗んだことだ !
so we stole the inheritances of very rich people.
And so there would be no fighting over their inheritance!
これで遺産争いは起きないね
きっと今頃 俺たちに感謝してるさ
They must surely be thanking us now!
そこでだ !
So that's where it's at.
We felt good when we did something good, so...
良いことをしたら
気分が良かったので
最後の仕事も良いことをしよう !
Let's do something good for our last job as well!
どんな?
Like?
We're gonna take the mafia's black money!
マフィアの黒い金を
奪ってやるのさ !
きやあ~~
アイザック力つこいいい!
You're so handsome, Isaac!
おいおい 気をつけろよ !
Hey, hey! Watch it!
Watch it!
気をつけろよ !
What did you say?!
何だと?
That is Eve Genoard, right?
あれがイブジ工ノア一ドだな
そのようです
It appears so.
Call her out.
呼ぴ出せ
どうやつてです力?
How should I do that?
It's your job to think of a way!
それを者えるのが お前の仕事だろ?
Do you want one?
食ベます力?
いらん!
No!
Understood.
分力りました
Yes? This is the Genoard family.
あい ジ工ノア一ド家
From the newspaper company?
新聞社力ら ?
ハア ハア ハア ハア
Yes. They said they have information for you about Dallas.
んだ ダラス坊ちゃまのこどで
お嬢様に話があるでえごとで
兄さんの?
About my brother?
新しい情報があるど力 ねえと力
Something about them having new information...
それがあ
The thing is, they hung up after saying they could only tell you in person.
電話でねぐって直接でなげりやあ
話せねえって切れ亡しまつてぇ
では行きましよう 新聞社に
Well then, let's go to the newspaper company.
オ工一
あ ジヤグジ一
Jacuzzi...
どうすれば あれだけの血が
つけられるの?
How on earth did all that blood get stuck up there?
Hey, all of you.
おい みんな
There's someone near the coupling between the train cars in front.
前の連結の所に何かいる
Let's all take a look on the count of two.
みんな せ一ので
のぞい亡みよぅぜ
Okay.
せ一の
One, two!
あ あ あれが… レイル卜レ一サ一?
Is that... Rail Tracer?
What are you doing here, girl?
何だ 姉ちやん 変な格好して
Walking around like that—
だあ !
きやああ !
てめつ !
オラツ
あ わつ 分力つたよ!
そいつらは解放する!
I understand already.
I'll let them go, so...
だ力ら勘弁し亡くれよ !
Please let me off the hook.
I have business with you though.
私が用があるのは
あなたのほうです
Amazing!
すげえ!
ー人でやっつけちまった!
You took care of them all by yourself!
Amazing!
すつごお~い!
ありがとう!
Thanks!
見ず知らずの俺たちを
助けてくれるなんてよ!
Saving complete strangers like ourselves...
You're a lifesaver!
姉ちゃんは命の恩人だ
Watch out. Why did we hit them?
気をつけろ なぜ はねた
申し訳ございません
突然 道に踊り出しまして
I'm sorry.
They suddenly danced out into the road.
何でも言ってくれ!
Ask us anything!
We'll do anything!
何でもするよ !
じやあ‥
Then, can you help me carry these four to my car?
この4人を車まで運ぶのを
手伝つて頂けません力?
曹蓄 ! イブ嬢が?
Kidnapped?! Eve was?!
はあ… 先ほど連絡がございまして
Yes...
I was just contacted with the news...
だ力ら言ったんだ!
どうする気なの 一体!? ああ?
That's why I told you!
What are you planning?!
I don't think Gustavo is planning to hurt Eve just yet.
まあ グス夕一ヴオもすぐにはイブ嬢を
どうに力しようとは者えないだろう
工レアン君も落ち着きたまえ
Calm down, Elean-kun.
し力しですねえ !
But sir...
心配なのは我が社の責任で
What worries me is the rivalry between the Gandors and the Runoratas is getting out of control because of us.
ガンド一ルとルノラ一夕の抗争を
厘つ亡しまうことだ
二コラス君 そのへんは
ちゃんと者え亡あるんだろうね?
Nicholas-kun, I hope you have taken that into consideration?
Yes, I've taken fool-proof measures to prevent such a thing from occurring.
はい そうならないように
万全の対策を
頼んだよ では行きたまえ
I'm counting on you.
Well, go now.
Director, he looks like he's scheming something!
ん~ 社長 あれはきつと
何力たくらんでる顔だよ!
I know.
分力っているよ
恐らく二コラス君は
Nicholas-kun is probably trying to make Gustavo clash with the Gandors head on...
意図的にグス夕一ヴオを
ガンド一ルにぶつけ亡
ほ瑛茜ヾ出ることを期待し亡いるのだ
and hopes for some interesting things to happen because of that.
彼なりに特秘事項につい乙
知りたいのだろう
I suppose he wants to learn more of that top secret in his own way.
社長 ほつとけつてこと ?
Director! You mean to leave him be?!
特秘事項 と はL え
Even though it's top secret, there's still a lot unknown about Dallas.
ダラスジ工ノア一ドに関し亡は
不明確なところも多い
Did he really become an Immortal?
本当に不死者となったのか
そうでないのか…
Or didn't he?
これで何かが明らかになれば
願つたり雛つたりだ
If we learn something from this, it's perfect for us.
それに我々が何もしなく亡も
Besides, even if we don't do anything,
ガンド一ルとルノラ一夕の抗争には
火種が加えられるよ
there will be some sparks between the Gandors and the Runoratas.
それはどういうこと ?
What do you mean by that?
伝説的殺し屋 ヴイ一ノこと
クレアス夕ンフイ一ルドが
The legendary assassin, Vino, or Claire Stanfield, is headed for New York.
二ユ一ヨ一クに向かつ亡いる
Apparently by invitation of Luck Gandor.
ラ ツク ガン ド一ルの招きだそうだ
ヴイ一ノ…
Vino...
He's on board the Flying Pussyfoot, the transcontinental express train from Chicago.
シ力ゴ発 大陸横断超特急
フライングプツシ一フツ 卜号でね
ふむ…
食つ亡も
大した知識になりそうにもないが…
I don't think I'll obtain a lot of knowledge from eating this one...
これも因果だな
This is also a matter of cause and effect.
工二ス
Ennis!
Yes.
はい
むう
dokomade mo tsuzuiteru hoshizora miagete utau
I sing, looking up into the endless starry night.
kagiriaru bokutachi no eien wo yume miru melody
A melody in a dream... about our limited eternity.
mune ni afureru itoshisa no mizu wa
This water of love, overflowing from my chest...
mirai no hate de dareka ni todoku darou
I wonder if it will reach someone in the future?
shinjite iruyo
I will believe in you.
harukana toki wo kake nukete
Transcending generations of time...
bokutachi no yobigoe wa itsuka ookina uta ni naru
Will our calls turn into a beautiful song one day?
ai wo tsumuide yukeru yo
You can start building your love,
ima wa mada konnani chiisana hikari dakedo
Though right now, the light is still faint.
Next ep
Preview
Everything Starts Aboard
the Advenna Avis
Miria, everything's going to start!
It's the beginning, right?
A-A-A-do-ve-na...
It's Advena!
It's the ship called A-do-ve-na A-ve-su.
It's the other way around, Isaac!
Ehh? A-ve-nisu Do-na...